Richard Scarry Papers 1997.0048
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Children's Literature, undated, 1965-1993
  - Richard Scarry's Busy Houses, 1981
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 560)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 561)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 562)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 563)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 564)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 565)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 566)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 567)
  - Richard Scarry's Busytown Pop-up Book, 1979
    - Sketches (11 pieces), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 568)
    - Color nesting sheets (4 pieces), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 569)
    - Black and white nesting sheets (2 pieces), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 570)
    - Ink artwork (cover-pages 8), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 571)
    - Ink artwork (pages 9-16), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 572)
    - Color artwork (cover), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 573)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 1-2), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 574)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 3-4), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 575)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 5-6), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 576)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 7-8), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 577)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 9-10), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 578)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 11-12), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 579)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 13-14), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 580)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 15-16), 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 581)
    - Nesting sheet A, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1310)
    - Nesting sheet B, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1311)
  - Richard Scarry's Color Book, 1976
    - Black and white acetate art (pages 1-2, 4 pieces), ca.1976 (Box OS:, Folder 582)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (front and back cover), ca.1976 (Box OS:, Folder 583)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 1-2), ca.1976 (Box OS:, Folder 584)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 3-4), ca.1976 (Box OS:, Folder 585)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 5-6), ca.1976 (Box OS:, Folder 586)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 7-8), ca.1976 (Box OS:, Folder 587)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 9-10), ca.1976 (Box OS:, Folder 588)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 11-12), ca.1976 (Box OS:, Folder 589)
  - Richard Scarry's Find Your ABC's, 1973
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 6-7), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 614)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 8-9), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 615)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 10-11), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 616)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 12-13), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 617)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 14-15), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 618)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 16-17), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 619)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 18-19), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 620)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 20-21), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 621)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 22-23), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 622)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 24-25), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 623)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 26-27), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 624)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 28-29), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 625)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 626)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 627)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 628)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 629)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 630)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 631)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 632)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 633)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 634)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 635)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 636)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 637)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 638)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 639)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 640)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 641)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1973 (Box OS:, Folder 642)
  - Richard Scarry's Stories to Color, 1978
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 986)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 987)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 988)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 989)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 990)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 991)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 992)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 993)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 994)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 995)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 996)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 997)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 998)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 999)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1000)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1001)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1002)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1003)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1004)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1005)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 48-49), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1006)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 50-51), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1007)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 52-53), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1008)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 54-55), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1009)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 56-57), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1010)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 58-59), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1011)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 60-61), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1012)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 62-63), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1013)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 64-65), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1014)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 66-67), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1015)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 68-69), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1016)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 70-71), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1017)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 72-73), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1018)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 74-75), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1019)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 76-77), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1020)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 78-79), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1021)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 80-81), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1022)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 82-83), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1023)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 84-85), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1024)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 86-87), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1025)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 88-89), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1026)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 90-91), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1027)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 92-93), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1028)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 94-95), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1029)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 96-97), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1030)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 98-99), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1031)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 100-101), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1032)
    - Black and white and text separations (pages 102-103), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1033)
    - Black and white and text separations (page 104), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1034)
  - The Runaway Steamshovel (unpublished)
    - Dummy and copy, undated (Box 1:, Folder 48)
  - The Supermarket Mystery, 1969
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 776)
    - Black and white and color separations (title page), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 777)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 778)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 8), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 779)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 9), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 780)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 781)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 782)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 783)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 784)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 18), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 785)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 19), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 786)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 787)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 788)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 789)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 790)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 791)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 792)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 793)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 34), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 794)
  - Take-along Library, 1986
    - Original black and white artwork (cover), ca. 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 49)
    - Color and black and white separations (cover), ca. 1986 (Box OS:, Folder 1303)
  - Tinker and Tanker, 1960
    - Typescripts and copy, undated (Box 1:, Folder 50)
    - Preliminary notes and sketches, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1304)
  - Tinker and His Friends (unpublished?)
    - Dummy and copy, undated (Box 1:, Folder 51)
  - Tinker and the Auto Parade (unpublished)
    - Dummy and copy, undated (Box 1:, Folder 52)
  - Toy Book, 1978
    - Preliminary artwork (16 pieces), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1035)
    - Acetate separations (15 pieces), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1036)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1037)
    - Black and white separations (page 3), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1038)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 4), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1039)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 5), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1040)
    - Black and white separations (page 6), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1041)
    - Black and white separations (page 7), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1042)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 8), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1043)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 9), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1044)
    - Black and white separations (page 10), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1045)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 12), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1046)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 13), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1047)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 16), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1048)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 17), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1049)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 19), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1050)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 20), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1051)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 21), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1052)
    - Black and white separations (page 22), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1053)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 24), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1054)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 25), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1055)
    - Black and white separations (page 26), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1056)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 28), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1057)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 29), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1058)
    - Black and white separations (page 31), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1059)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 32), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1060)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 3), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1061)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 4), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1062)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 8), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1063)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 9), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1064)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 12), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1065)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 13), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1066)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 16), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1067)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 19), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1068)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 22), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1069)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 23), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1070)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 24), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1071)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 25), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1072)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 28), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1073)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 29), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1074)
    - Mechanical drawings (page 32), ca. 1978 (Box OS:, Folder 1075)
  - What Do People Do All Day?, 1968
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1127)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1128)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1129)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1130)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1131)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1132)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1133)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1134)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1135)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1136)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1137)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1138)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1139)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1140)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1141)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1142)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1143)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1144)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1145)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1146)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1147)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1148)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 48-49), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1149)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 50-51), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1150)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 52-53), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1151)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 54-55), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1152)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 56-57), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1153)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 58-59), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1154)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 60-61), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1155)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 62-63), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1156)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 64-65), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1157)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 66-67), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1158)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 68-69), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1159)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 70-71), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1160)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 72-73), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1161)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 74-75), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1162)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 76-77), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1163)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 78-79), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1164)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 80-81), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1165)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 82-83), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1166)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 84-85), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1167)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 86-87), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1168)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 88-89), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1169)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 90-91), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1170)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 92-93), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1171)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 94-95), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1172)
    - Proof, earlier corrected proof, and new artwork (page 15), 1 Oct. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 1173)
    - Original black and white artwork (page 74), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1174)
    - Paste-up (cover), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1175)
    - Original black and white artwork (cover), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1176)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 2-3), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1177)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 4-5), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1178)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 6-7), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1179)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 8-9), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1180)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 10-11), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1181)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 12-13), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1182)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 14-15), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1183)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 16-17), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1184)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 18-19), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1185)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 20-21), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1186)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 22-23), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1187)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 24-25), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1188)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 26-27), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1189)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 28-29), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1190)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 30-31), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1191)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 32-33), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1192)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 34-35), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1193)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 36-37), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1194)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 38-39), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1195)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 40-41), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1196)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 42-43), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1197)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 44-45), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1198)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 46-47), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1199)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 48-49), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1200)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 50-51), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1201)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 52-53), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1202)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 54-55), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1203)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 56-57), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1204)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 58-59), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1205)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 60-61), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1206)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 62-63), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1207)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 70-71), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1208)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 72-73), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1209)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 74-75), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1210)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 76-77), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1211)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 78-79), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1212)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 80-81), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1213)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 90-91), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1214)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 92-93), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1215)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 94-95), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1216)
  - Unidentified book dummy with wheels, undated (Box 4:, Folder 71)
  - Unidentified scroll dummy A, undated (Box 2:)
  - Unidentified scroll dummy B, undated (Box 3:)
  - Unidentified black and white artwork, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1305)
  - Unidentified artwork, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1306)
  - Unidentified black and white cover art (2 pieces), undated (Box OS:, Folder 1307)
- Series III: Ephemera, 1989-1997